A Guide to the Markle Foundation records, Accessions 1997-2008, Record Group 4 FA785
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 2008:073, 1989-2006; 9; 38.11 Cubic Feet 28 standard record storage boxes, boxes 190-217.
  - Web White and Blue (WWB), 11
    - Markle Foundation - Web, White and Blue (WWB) - Catherine Clark (993038BP), 1999 (Box 209, Folder 20-21)
    - Web, White and Blue (WWB) Campaign - Catherine Clark (J99003), 1998-2000 (Box 209, Folder 22-26)
    - Web, White and Blue (WWB) Campaign - Catherine Clark (J99003), 1998-2000; Includes digital media. (Box 210, Folder 1-3)
    - Web, White and Blue (WWB) Promotion - Catherine Clark (J99005), 2000 (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Markle - Understanding USA, 1999-2000 (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Markle Foundation - Web, White and Blue (WWB) - Zoe Baird (001013BP), 1999 (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - Freedom Channel, Inc. - Douglas Bailey (001013BP-A), 1999-2000 (Box 210, Folder 7-8)
    - Freedom Channel, Inc. - Douglas Bailey (001013BP-B), 1999 (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - Mindshare, Internet Campaign, LLC - Jonah Seiger (001013BP-C), 2000 (Box 210, Folder 10)
    - Public Strategies Group, LLC - Michael McCurry (001013BP-D), 1999 (Box 210, Folder 11)
    - Tracy Calvan - Consultant for Youth-e-Vote - Web, White and Blue, WWB 2000 (001013BP-E) (Box 210, Folder 12)
    - Implementation and Construction for WWB 2000 - Michael Cornfield, Consultant (001013BP-F) (Box 210, Folder 13)
    - Web, White and Blue (WWB) (Non-grant) - Carin Dessauer (001013BP-G), 2001 (Box 210, Folder 14)
    - Steven Clift Consulting-Publicus.net (Non-grant) - Steve Clift (001013BP-H), 2001 (Box 210, Folder 15)
    - Mike Mc Curry (Non-grant) (001013BP-I), 2001 (Box 210, Folder 16)
    - Douglas Bailey (001013BP-J), 2001 (Box 210, Folder 17)
    - Mindshare, Internet Campaign, LLC - Jonah Seiger (001013BP-K), 2001 (Box 210, Folder 18)
    - Freedom Channel, Inc.-Youth-e-Vote - Douglas Bailey (001013BP-L), 2000 (Box 210, Folder 19-21)
    - Web, White and Blue (WWB 2000) - Oversized (Box 211)
    - Web, White and Blue (WWB 2000) (003041BP), 2000-2001 (Box 212, Folder 1-2)
    - Steven Clift Consulting - Steven Clift (003041BP-B), 2000 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - California Voting Foundation - Kim Alexander (003041BP-C), 2000 (Box 212, Folder 4-5)
    - Knowledge Networks - (003041BP-D), 2000 (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Carnegie Mellon University (003041BP-E), 2000 (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - University of San Diego - Skip Lupia (003041BP-F), 2000-2001 (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - Evalutation of WWB Election Project - Arthur Lupia (003041BP-G), 2000-2001 (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - University of California - Sean Cain (003041BP-H), 2001 (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - Evaluation - Michael Cornfield (003041BP-I), 2000 (Box 212, Folder 11)
    - Web, White and Blue (WWB) Background files (Box 212, Folder 12-14)
    - Web, White and Blue (WWB) Retreat (Box 212, Folder 15-16)
    - Web, White and Blue (WWB) - Edelman - Public Relations Worldwide, 2001 (Box 212, Folder 17)
    - Web, White and Blue (WWB) Clippings (Box 212, Folder 18)
    - Web, White and Blue (WWB) Media (Box 212, Folder 19)
    - Web, White and Blue (WWB) Press (Box 212, Folder 20-21)
    - Web, White and Blue (WWB) News Coverage and Clippings (Box 212, Folder 22)
    - Web, White and Blue (WWB) News Coverage and Clippings (Box 213, Folder 1-5)
    - WWB 2000 - Edelman Public Relations Clipping Book (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - WWB 2000 - Public Campaign Overview (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - WWB: Did It Make A Difference - Conference, 2001 February 15 (Box 213, Folder 8)
    - WWB Evaluation Transcripts (Box 213, Folder 9-10)
    - Youth-e-Vote.net, 2001 (Box 213, Folder 11)
    - Web, White and Blue (WWB) Campain 3, 1998 (Box 213, Folder 12-17)
    - Web, White and Blue (WWB) Campain 5, 1998-1999 (Box 213, Folder 12-29)
    - Web, White and Blue (WWB) Campain 5, 1998-1999 (Box 214, Folder 1-6)
    - WWB - Schneider Evaluation, 2000 (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - The Daily Standard (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - WWB - Robinson, Lerer and Montgomery (RLM), 2000 (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - Meeting with WWB.com Partners, 2000 March 22 (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - WWB Participants, 2000 May (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - WWB Partners, 2001 June 9 (Box 214, Folder 12)
    - WWB.Orgs, 2000 (Box 214, Folder 13)
    - 2000 Politics Online Conference (Box 214, Folder 14)
    - Board Presentation, 2000 June 7 (Box 214, Folder 15)
    - WWB Evaluation, 2000-2001 (Box 214, Folder 16-19)
    - Web Design (Box 214, Folder 20)
    - Steve Clift WWB, 2000 (Box 214, Folder 21)
    - WWB 2000, 1992-2005 (Box 214, Folder 22-23)
    - Web, White and Blue, 1998-2001 (Box 214, Folder 24)
    - WWB Background, 1999-2000 (Box 214, Folder 25)
    - WWB Evaluation Coordinator (Box 214, Folder 26)
    - Fearless - Website Draft Plan (Box 214, Folder 27)
    - WWB 2000 Charter Site, 2001 (Box 214, Folder 28)
    - WWB Advisory Board, 2000 July 27 (Box 214, Folder 29)
    - WWB Academics (Box 214, Folder 30)
    - WWB Democracy Row Participants (Box 214, Folder 31)
    - Retreat (Box 214, Folder 32)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 214, Folder 33)
    - Public Relations Bid (Box 214, Folder 34)
    - WWB Policy Editorial, 2000 (Box 214, Folder 35)
    - WWB Anchors, 1998-1999 (Box 214, Folder 36)
    - Public Agenda - DNET Proposal (Box 214, Folder 37)
    - Markle Foundation - Web, White and Blue (WWB) (993038BP), 1999-2000 (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Project Vote Smart, 2000-2001 (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Public Relations - Marketing, 2000 (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - Public Agenda, 1996-2001 (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - Public Strategies - Internet Democracy Project, 2000 (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Quarium, 2000 (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - Research WWB (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - Peter Shane, 2000 (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - Talking Points (Box 215, Folder 9)
    - United Nations TV Forum 2000 (Box 215, Folder 10)
    - VNR (Box 215, Folder 11)
    - ECRI Report - Lerner (Box 215, Folder 12)
    - Rolling Cyber Debate, 2000 (Box 215, Folder 13)
    - Seiger Proposal (Box 215, Folder 14)
    - Conference, 2000-2001 (Box 215, Folder 15)
    - Executive Summary - Evaluation of WWB, 2000-2001 (Box 215, Folder 16)
    - WWB - Contracts (Box 215, Folder 17)
    - FreedomChannel.com - Youth-e-Vote.net (Box 215, Folder 18)
    - WWB Implementation Plan, 1999-2000 (Box 215, Folder 19)
    - WWB 2000: Preliminary Campaign Proposal - WWB 2000: Preliminary Campaign Proposal (Box 215, Folder 20)
    - WWB - Public Relations, 2001 (Box 215, Folder 21)
    - WWB - Transcripts, Includes digital media. (Box 215, Folder 22)
    - White House Project - An Online Conference Envisioning Internet Usage by the Next President, 2000 (Box 215, Folder 23)
    - WWB - Teen.com, 1999 (Box 215, Folder 24)
    - Regis University - Joan Conners, 1996-2000 (Box 215, Folder 25)
    - WWB - Tent Card, 2000 (Box 215, Folder 26)
    - Tools and Resources (Box 215, Folder 27)
    - Mike Weiksner, 2000 (Box 215, Folder 28)
  - Oxygen, 12
    - Oxygen - Markle Foundation Pulse - Third Quarter 2000 Summary (993039BP) (Box 215, Folder 29)
    - Oxygen - Markle Foundation Pulse - Advisory Board Meeting Briefing Book (993039BP), 2000 September 27 (Box 215, Folder 30)
    - FACCT - Markle Foundation - Oxygen - Life on the Line - Final Report, 2004 (Box 215, Folder 31)
    - Oxygen - Markle Foundation - Life on the Line (033021BP), 2003 (Box 216, Folder 1-5)
    - Oxygen Pulse, LLC (993040BP), 1999 (Box 216, Folder 6-13)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Pulse QI: Research and Questionnaire (Box 216, Folder 14)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Spot Poll: Women and Political Giving (Box 216, Folder 15)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Survey QI: Section 1 - Women's Political Engagement Report (Box 216, Folder 16)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Pulse Second Signature Survey (Box 216, Folder 17)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Carla Seal Warner (Box 216, Folder 18)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Oxygen Press Releases (Box 216, Folder 19)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Oxygen Pulse Research (Box 216, Folder 20)
    - Oxygen (993040BP) - Oxygen Pulse Proposals (Box 216, Folder 21)
    - Oxygen (993040BP) - Oxygen: Milllword Brown (Box 216, Folder 22)
    - Oxygen (993040BP) - Oxygen: Penn and Schoen (Box 216, Folder 23)
    - Oxygen (993040BP) - Oxygen: Press Clippings (Box 216, Folder 24)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Oxygen Spot Poll Brief: Political Brief (Box 216, Folder 25)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Oxygen-Markle Foundation Status Report (Box 216, Folder 26)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Oxygen-Markle Foundation Business Plan (Box 216, Folder 27)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Advisory Board (Box 216, Folder 28)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Be Fearless - Be Fearless with Your Vote: Press Release (Box 216, Folder 29)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Concept Paper - The Parent's Web Guide to Interactive Media Products for Children (Box 216, Folder 30)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Correspondence (Box 216, Folder 31)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Meeting Notes (Box 216, Folder 32)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Oxygen-Markle Foundation Definition (Box 216, Folder 33)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Oxygen Legal (Box 216, Folder 34)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Markle Foundation-Oxygen Media (Box 216, Folder 35)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Oxygen Meeting, 2000 June 2 (Box 216, Folder 36)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Oxygen Press (Box 216, Folder 37)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Oxygen Pitch to Markle Foundation (Box 216, Folder 38)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Oxygen Pulse: Ongoing (Box 216, Folder 39)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Oxygen Pulse: Releases (Box 216, Folder 40)
    - Oxygen (993039BP) - Oxygen Re-Tool (Box 216, Folder 41)
    - Oxygen (993039BP-B) - Oxygen Media-Markle Foundation (Box 216, Folder 42)
    - Oxygen (993039BP-B) - Lygeia Ricciardi, 1999 (Box 216, Folder 43)
    - Foundation for Accountability (FACCT) (993039BP-B), 2002 (Box 216, Folder 44)
    - Foundation for Accountability (FACCT) (993039BPC-A), 2001 (Box 216, Folder 45)
  - Foundation Non-Programmatic Grants, 13
    - Council on Foundations - Ridings (DG99216), 1999 (Box 215, Folder 32)
    - The Foundation Center - Engelhardt (D98331), 1998 (Box 215, Folder 33)
    - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers - Bryan (D99101), 1998 (Box 215, Folder 34)
    - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers - Bryan (D993032), 1999 (Box 215, Folder 35)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - Stapleton (G96111), 1996-1999 (Box 215, Folder 36-37)
    - Rockefeller Archive Cente - Byers (001011BP), 1999-2001 (Box 215, Folder 38)
    - Rockefeller Archive Cente - Stapleton (001002DG), 1999-2000 (Box 215, Folder 39)
  - Publications, 14
    - Achieving Electronic Connectivity in Healthcare, 2004 July (Box 217)
    - About Connecting for Health: Pamphlet, 2002-2004 (Box 217)
    - Toward a Framework for Internet Accountability (Box 217)
    - Executive Summary of CASS (Box 217)
    - A Roadmap: Global Policy Making for Information and Communications Technologies, 2002 June (Box 217)
    - Creating a Trusted Information Network for Homeland Security, 2003; 1 book, 2 spiral (Box 217)
    - Mobilizing Information to Prevent Terrorism, 2006 (Box 217)
    - The Markle Foundation: Task Force on National Security in Information Age (Box 217)
    - Health Affairs: Health Information Technology, 2005 September (Box 217)
    - Results Book: Common Framework for Health, 2005 January (Box 217)
    - Improving Life in the Information Age, 1999 July; 2 copies (Box 217)
    - Understanding Healthcare (Box 217)
    - Foreign Affairs: Governing the Internet, 2002 November; 2 copies (Box 217)
    - WTO, E-Commerce and Information Technologies, 2005 (Box 217)
    - Collected Essays 1969-1997: Lloyd Morrisett (Box 217)
    - Information Technologies for Better Health (Box 217)
    - Connecting for Health: The Data Standards Working Group, 2003 June (Box 217)
    - Connecting for Health: The Privacy and Security Working Group, 2003 June (Box 217)
    - Connecting for Health: The Steering Group, 2003 June (Box 217)
    - Connecting Americans to Their Healthcare: Final Report (Box 217)
    - Linking Healthcare Information: Proposed Methods to Improving Care and Protecting Privacy, 2005 February (Box 217)
    - Financial, Legal and Organizational Approaches to Achieving Electronic Connectivity in Healthcare, 2004 October (Box 217)
    - Fast Company: Fast Foundation, by Zoe Baird, 2001 February (Box 217)
    - The Sillicon Alley Reporter, by Zoe Baird, 2000 (Box 217)
    - Growing up with Interactive Media (Box 217)
    - Serving the World's Poor, Profitably, 2002 (Box 217)
    - Creating a Development Dynamic, 2001 July (Box 217)
    - Children and Interactive Media: Research Compendium Update, 2002 November (Box 217)
    - Task Force on National Security in the Information Age: Pamphlet (Box 217)
    - Connecting for Health: The Perosnal Health Working Group, 2003 June; 2 copies (Box 217)
    - Surveying Internet Usage and Impact in Five Chinese Cities, 2005 October (Box 217)
    - Approaching the Internet in Chinese Small Cities, 2003 October (Box 217)
    - Surveying Internet Usage and Impact in Twelve Chinese Cities, 2003 October (Box 217)